<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ProcessingData>
  <Positive>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>The value of exercise in a treatment plan is well documented and understood. No need to go down that path. But this morning on the treadmill I wondered which is most beneficial. : for pd treatment cardio or weights. So as much for fun as well as education if u cud only pick one cardio or weight training which wud it be and why? I go first and pick weights in that one can emphasize reps or max weights. Stave off muscle atrophy and weakness</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Hi Michael,At the age of 61 with challenges ahead, I would pick cardio. Though I could benefit from weight training, I'm more concerned with maintaining a heallthy heart and being able to take a walk without tiring too soon. I think cardio gives you addtional benefits such as weight loss, more restful sleep (we all hope), and generally a better outlook. My first priority is to keep moving. Good question!</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Michael,I have been going to cardiac rehab at a local hospital for 3 1/2 years. Started one month after having open heart surgery. At rehab I use a treadmill, bicycle, arm machine, stepper, light dumbbells, and do stretching. All are important to me.If I had to choose between cardiac exercises and lifting weights I would reluctantly give up the weights. I would continue with cardiac rehab because it is in my opinion helping with my heart health and PD.Edit changed the word weights to dumbbells</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>I woud not give up on one for the other. The benefits are different between cardiovascular and weights and we need both. There is a third as pet that might be considered. Agility/flexibility/coordination training. This can be in the form of dancing, taichi, yoga or martial arts. I do cardiovascular in the form of high intensity interval training, weights and karate.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Let me add a third option, or of cardio is option 1, I do this as option 1a. I have found that stretching is very important with PD as our bodies tighten. For example, the stoop a lot of PD patients have. As part of stretching I use a couple of different elastic bands. So my approach is cardio, stretching and bands for strength. It results in a very portable gym.Also, I wear 2 1/2 lbs wrist weights and 5 lb ankle weights when I stretch and do bands. I actually started the weights because a physical therapist suggested that the weights may help my golf swing. She said that a lot of PD patients have difficulty sensing there position in space (a lot of PD patients tilt one way or another when standing). Adding the weights can help our biofeedback mechanism. Sounded sort of far fetched to me, but now when I am warming up at the driving range prior to teeing off, I hit about a dozend balls wearing the weights. It does really help.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>I was put on 1 sentiment 25/100 3x a day and soon developed a intense shaking of my leg about 30 minutes before the next pill. At night my leg would shake for 2 hours straight. I thought it was because the meds were wearing off. My MDS put me on admenadine and Mirapex. I also developed dystonia. When I went back to my MDS she reduced my carbidopa/levbadopa to 1/2 a 25/100 3x a day. Took me off admenadine but left me on 1/2 a .25 Merapix. No more tremor, and I feel great.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>When changing to the University of Florida Movement Disorder Center with world reknown Dr. Okun, I was found to be over medicated on Reqiip, Primidone and Sinemet It took 6 difficult weeks to come off the meds and reintroduced Requip and Sinemet at lower dosages and dropped Primidone totally. It was better and then Rytary was approved in January and in March, I started Rytary and small dosage Requip and am doing real well. I have had Parkinson's over 8 years. I say, "I have Parkinsons but Parkinsons does not have me."</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Fatigue can be a result of PD, the medications taken for PD or not related to the PD at all (oh the joy of PD). As the inspector suggests, go see your GP. I attributed a number of things to PD that were being caused elsewhere. Felt a lot better once it was addressed.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>I believe that if any individual, whether you have PD or not, follows these basic guidelines of eating the right foods, getting plenty of sleep and exercise regularly will generally feel better than if you don't. However, if you have PD, it become more important to successfully do all 3 and if you don't the dropoff you will have will be more severe than a person w/o PD.Greenjade: Glad the early morning exercise help. I also find a gentle exercise first thing in the morning tends to set me up to have a better day. It's interesting that my body tends not to respond the same way if the exercise is strenuous first thing in the morning. Also, may I point out that your own words indicate there are some things you do better today than pre PD.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Any one have excessive sweating with floricef?  I take 0.2mg over 12 hours and midodrine .20 mg over 12 hrs.  Also Northera 600mg over 12 hrs.A rare side effect listed for floricef is excessive sweating which I have as a big problem.  I take all this for orthostatic hypotension.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>I've been on Rytary for 8 months with one side effect-morning fatigue-and I take a large dose.  I was taking 12 of the 195MG 4 X day.  I discussed the fatigue issue with my MDS and he directed that I add 2 additional capsules at bedtime (so now I take 14/day).The morning fatigue issue disappeared.Other than some recent wearing off issues, I'm very happy with Rytary.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Thanks Slumpy.  I see the starting dose was 3 times a day.  My doc wants me to start with 2 capsules, every 4-5 hrs. Does this seem normal?  Is constipation also a problem?</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Yes, that sounds correct!  I take 3 capsules every 4 hrs, so 2 for you is most likely the correct dosage.Yes constipation is a problem but I blame that on PD, in general, not particularly on Rytary.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Last month, I complained to my Movement Disorders Specialist that I had trouble falling asleep and problems staying asleep if I woke up in the night.  I had been following the recommendations of Eric Ahlskog in his "The New Parkinson's Disease Treatment Book" (take a full dose of regular levodopa 1 hour before bed, a tablet of controlled release levodopa when my head hits the pillow, and a full dose of regular levodopa if I wake in the night).  This worked some times, but was not the complete answer.  My Movement Disorders Specialist asked what kept me from falling back to sleep if I woke up, and I replied that it was tremors, especially in my legs.  He exclaimed that he had the perfect solution to my problem: mirtazapine .  Although mirtazapine is an antidepressant and I am far from being depressed, it has an off-label use for eliminating the tremor of PD.  Back home, I did some research and confirmed this. The effect was first noticed by a woman with PD who was prescribed mirtazapine and then noticed that her hands no longer shook when she played bridge.From the first night I took mirtazapine (7.5 mg), I have slept the best I have in years.  If I wake in the middle of the night, I fall right back to sleep.  But that's not all!  After a week, I noticed that I was dyskinetic more than usual, suggesting that my levodopa doses were too high.  I have now backed off from 12.5 to 8.25 grams of levodopa daily and feel BETTER.  I am now doing activities that have been forbidden to me for the past 4 years such as walking around downtown after having dinner with friends.  I also feel that I could return to work, despite having retired in 2011 because of PD.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>I see you have not reached the point where you have had ENOUGH with PD and will choose the meds as a relief.  Carbidopa levodopa is dopamine replacement, where the brain is not making enough.  I have progressed beyond that still, now to where I have had DBS surgery.  It makes my life livable again and I am not looking back.  Being able to go to the bathroom first thing in the morning and being able to stand and not miss the toilet bowl can be quite the pleasure. Being able to continue working is another.  I am still taking my dopamine meds , but in lesser quantity.  Good luck in making the decision!</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Can't really say anything about Mirapex but I am on ropinerole (Requip), it's brother. On max dose. Little orthostatic hypotension. Haven't had any hallucinations, compulsions or daytime sleepiness. So as with most drugs some people get a side effect some don't. Can't find any black box warning but there are some who are calling for one. As per Michael let your doctor know if you have those side effects.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Mirapex is in the same drug class with ropinerole.  They are called dopamine agonists (they act like dopamine).  Minimal side effects.  Sometime transient nausea.  Can drop your BP like so many other PD drugs, but it is usually treatable or you get used to it.  Information out today supports having a systolic (top number) in BP &lt;120 as a means to lessen mortality, so this may be a good side effect.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>I was diagnosed with Parkinson's around 2008 back then doctors kept changing my medication until they got it right. later, I was on the patch which was working fairly well until the insurance stop covering it. For a while now I'm on Mirapex and have gone down to 88lb. Doctors told me Mirapex cause anorexia so I'm being taken off the medicine. Has anyone on PLM ever heard of this side effects from Mirapex?</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>As pointed out by a number of people sleeping and PD don't mix well.  The approach that seems to work for me is:1)  When  you wake up, just go with it and get up.  Like Parkinsons Pete, I tee off early frequently.2)  The only meds I take for sleeping is my Parkinson's meds.  If find if my Parkinson's symptoms are under control I am more relaxed and I sleep better.  Generally that means I wake up every 3 hours.  I generally go right back to sleep after taking the meds.3) Add an afternoon siesta to your schedule.  I find it easier to get 7 to 8 hours of sleep in 2 separate blocks (ie. 5 + 2).4) About once every 7 to 10 days I get 9 to 10 hours a sleep (in 3 hours blocks) because it's time to fully recharge.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>I fought insomnia for more than 6 months. 3 hours a night, even for a 5-6 hour person had me exhausted. I wanted to avoid another drug more than getting sleep.....for too long. After tryin a melatonin and a few other things, I ended up with 1 mg clonezapam - I can sleep 5-6 hours again and feel great!</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Melatonin, I tried that.  No joy (for me).  Doc changed my line up (carbadopa-levodopa plus ropinerol/requip) to where I'm only taking the ropinerol at 6-7pm; for me, that slows me down a bit, I get sleepy at least and have been getting some rest 'til around 4am.  I've had best results when I combine: no alcohol, lots of fresh air that day, some exercise, stretching, and a peaceful evening... add to that a cool, dark and quiet environment. So... when I don't sleep... I'm getting this awful sensation in my spine that runs down to my leg, and it makes me "twitch."  It doesn't hurt or anything, it's just a little twerk that makes me very uncomfortable... so then I have to move... I move, settle down, but then the little signal comes back again... anyone ever get that?  It's maddening!  Like I want to crack my back or something.. uggh.  Only cure is to get up, walk around, stretch, more stretching until the little electrons are gone....</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>I ust admit I have been sleeping pretty good lately.  I only wake up two or three time a night and can usually go back to sleep quickly.I believe I owe that to Melatonin.  Which I started about 5 weeks ago.In fact I woke up this morning and my bride said "You were singing in your sleep last night"  She said it was beautiful.  I had to laugh.  I am the only guy I know who was asked not to try out for the choir in a Baptist church that only had about 100 members.  So I know it could not have been pretty</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Thanks, y'all. After forum discussions and some correspondence with Elliecat, I started  two-a-day Sinemet about a month ago (mid-morning and mid-to-late afternoon) with my neuro's approval even tho I was doing well. It did actually improve the fluidity of my handwriting, which was my biggest frustration. I believe it's also making me feel better generally. I've even noticed that what I thought was just age-related droopiness on my right eye also seems to be less. Maybe it's actually been facial masking. I said I'd try it for a month. I intend to keep going</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>I get that burning and tingling occasionally at night.  I take 2 of those same tablets three times a day and one of the ER at night. Except for at night my symptoms seem to be managed, not perfectly but good.  I can function and think (for the most part Wink).</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>I was DX 18 months ago, age 70. I take 1/2 a 25/100 plus 1/2 .0125 MeripexMeripex 4x a day. I was taking a whole pill 4x a day but developed dyskinesia that lasted up to 2 hours at night.. Now I am ok but notice the wearing off occasionally.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Doing great with my 8 to 10 C/L per day. Added 200mg comtan to extend effective on time.  4 times a day with 2 25/100 C/L + 1 200mg Comtan.  Up to 2 addition 25/100 to assist with dystonia at night as needed.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>I have try and use Zandopa for one monch with good results. The last 3 days when I taken Zandopa and is kicking in. I'm not feeling good. I have headache, illness, dizzy &amp; bad balans. My dosage is 1tsp/ 3times per day Anyone feeling the same and could help me?</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>I found that Sinemet worked just fine by itself. I especially didn't like the sugar in Zandoapa.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
  </Positive>
  <Negative>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>I've been taking 25/100 mg Sinemet for about two years, one pill three times a day. At the suggestion of my neurologist I've increased the dosage to 1 1/2 pills three times a day and have been on this increased dosage for almost two weeks. My freezing actually seems to have gotten worse during this time and I also seem to feel more stiffness. Instead of my movements showing improvement, they're going the other direction. I'm wondering if anyone else has had their sinemet dosage increased and experienced similar results.Mark this post as helpful</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Increased to 2    25/100  3 times a day  and 1   50/200 at bed time.Shaking is getting worse. Now when tremor starts in right arm I have to grab it to stop it from really shaking. Noticing some head movements and stiff neck. tend to tip my head back to much</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Lately, I have been experiencing more fatigue than usual.  I still exercise routinely so that doesn't seem to be the problem. However, there has been considerable stress for me in the past few months (surprise birthday for me, spinal surgery for my wife, oldest granddughter marrying and, of course, the holidays.Anyone else having more fatigue than usual and how do you handle all of it?</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Fatigue is probably my #1 problem. I have terrible time sleeping at night and i'm always tired. I really don't know how I made it though work when I was working. I was a nurse who worked 12 hr shifts and I physically couldn't handle the job anymore! Plus my twitching and balance problems made working in delivery room impossible. Its very hard at time because I am 49 and diagnosed at 45 just never expected PD to be a part of my life!</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Well, I have run into yet another concern with Rytary.  I had several attempts with using it, both times I decided that the cost factor was prohibitive when compared with the benefits.  I went back on carbidopa/levodopa 25-100 mg.  I found that I could better control the dosing to fit into my daily routines.  BUT THE BIGGEST issue that I am dealing with now is an extreme increase in appetite which is leading to weight gain!  I traced the symptoms back to the onset of taking Rytary.  Anybody have this experience, and what did you do about it?  Right before this series of events, I spent a week in the hospital, three days intubated in ICU.  Don't know if that contributed to the problem or what.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>I must say that my source is just my neurologist PA.  She has had significant contact with patients on a daily basis.  I should have stated this as my information contact.  And I myself had a negative experience on both times that I tried RYTARY.  Sick in a way that was not really explainable, because I had never been ill in quite the same way any other time.  I realize from looking at other post that the quite a few had not had the ill feeling, but quite a few did.  To the point that they went off of the medication.  This "ill" feeling is what made me inquire as to what the delivery system consisted of, since I never have that feeling with CL in it's original, fast acting way.  I might also mention that I had Bariatric surgery thirteen years ago, and have been on the CL for fourteen years without any significant problems, other than on-off times that required dose adjustments.  So that's another piece of the puzzle.Don't you find that all of use have many "puzzle pieces" to put into this mix?</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Slumpy,  I too seem to struggle with the constant ups and downs of regularity, so maybe the Rytary isn't any worse than regular C/L?Michael123, I don't see my MDS until the end of December and have been reluctant to start Rytary prior to talking with him.  First he said to take 2-Rytary at night to combat RLS, then he changed that to Requip, and 2-Rytary every 4-5 hrs. during the day.  Presently I'm on regular C/L.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Hi Lexie,Good to hear from you again.  I have moved south for the winter, from the Vancouver BC area to South Florida.  Yes, the Mirtazapine seems to mute my REM sleep disorder, but does not prevent my acting out dreams.I would reiterate that mirtazapine is the most effective pharmaceutical for PD after levodopa.I too would like to hear from anyone successfully taking Mirtazapine.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>It is so good to hear from you too!  I am so happy you are doing better and also that you are able to "winter" in Florida.  As you know, this cold/damp N.W. weather is tough to take when you have PD.Re: REM Sleep Behavior Disorder, I also take 1 mg of clonazepam along with 15mg of Mirtazapine to control my night time "babbling" and my acting out of dreams.  However, when I am very stressed, neither medications can keep me quiet or keep me from acting out my dreams (which a few years ago resulted in a broken left big toe and 3 surgeries to "repair" it!).  It is good we have (our poor sleep deprived!) partners looking out for us at night.Wishing you continued success with your Mirtazapine!</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>I was diagnosed with PD over a year ago the doctor want me to start medication but I'm so afraid on the meds because of my sensitivity to so many meds over the years I can't even take pain meds and I read about all the side effects and is scares me. My question is , how bad are they really? how about mirapex? Etc..</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Mirapex can have severe side effects.  It has a black box warning regarding sleep attacks.  when I was taking Mirapex, I couldn't stay awake during the day and could not sleep at night.  It can be the source of aggressive-compulsive disorders such as gambling and other excessive behaviors.  in my case, my MDS had to take off mirapex when I had significant edema in my lower legs.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Does anyone besides me have trouble sleeping?  It seems like I may sleep on alternate nights.  It is not unusual for me to only sleep may three or four nights per week.  Is this typical of Parkinsons?  I have tried Melatonin, up to 6mg at a time so far....sometimes it helps but most times it doesn't.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Sleep is difficult to get.  I used melatonin for a few months.  It stopped being effective.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Sleep is difficult, usually 3-4 hrs if i'm lucky. I've tried melatonin, Ambien , temazapam, zaleplon, and Lunesta. The only one that seemed to work was temazapam,but was taken off drug due to side effects.  I usually crash about once every ten days and get 6 hours sleep.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Same here JackAndrews, before pd was front and center I could and did sleep anywhere!  My work required a lot of travel, and my colleagues teased that I could literally sleep standing up while waiting in line at airport terminals! That was then, this is now-- sleep is elusive, not restful, and once awake I can't go back to sleep--be it 1:00 am or 3:00 am.  I try to not stress about it.  I usually get up and find some quiet thing to occupy myself with-- I've crocheted a lot of blankets theses past couple years!</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Hi I am taking Sinemet for Parkinson's for 1and1/2 years. Recently it started to make me lose my balance and fall. I know it's the Sinemet because I take my last dose at 5 pm and when that wears off at about 8 pm I do not have the problem again until I begin taking the Sinemet again the next morning at 8 am. I have fallen badly so many times I now have to use a walker. Has anyone had this or heard of this? Any suggestions on how to fix it? Thank you. Barbara</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Maybe you are starting to have low blood pressure issues. Sinemet will make it worse. I have orthostatic hypertension. When I started sinemet it made it worse. So now I have to take Florinef to help raise my blood pressure. If you find you get dizzy going from a seated position to a standing position it might be because of a drop in blood pressure. To test this you need to take your BP at  a seated position then a standing position and see if there is a drop in pressure.`</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>Hi Yes I told my neurologist and he didn't believe me. He said I needed more Sinemet but I know I needed less because when the Sinemet wears off I don't have the problem. I went to another neurologist who lowered my dose of Sinemet. The symptom is a little better on the lower dose. The falling doesn't get bad until I take my 2 pm dose. After I take my 5 pm dose - my last dose of the day, I stay in bed until 8 pm when it wears off so I don't fall. The balance problem gets worse as the day goes on and I take more Sinemet. I don't take a lot of drugs. I take thyroid and a small dose of Zantac in the morning. I take .25 mugs of lorezapam at night. I don't know what to do because I need the Sinemet but it causes this problem. Any suggestions would be appreciated Barbara</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>My doctor just increased my dosage of Carbidopa/Levo 25/100 to 10 tablets a day taken in 3 hour intervals plus 1 ER 50/200 at bedtime. I told my doctor that after I take them a get short term burning and tingling sensation in my feet that lasts a hour or so. He says it must be something else causing it. HELP.... Does the dosage seem high and has any one else experienced the burning sensation</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
    <DataItem Date="0001-01-01T00:00:00">
      <Text>I am new and take only 2 / day, low dosage. I just started and hope it works. My body shakes, its hard to walk,my balance is bad, and I have difficulty grabbing things with my fingers/hands. Thats just for starters.</Text>
      <Stars>0</Stars>
    </DataItem>
  </Negative>
  <Neutral />
</ProcessingData>